JIVKO-VALENTINO

RADOSAVLEVICI

SOFTWARE ARCHITECT/CTO



CONTACT

https://markjivko.com

@markjivko

stephino.team@gmail.com

github.com/Stephino

PROFILE

Full-stack Software Architect turned Chief Technology Officer.

13+ years of experience in professional software development.

7+ years of experience in guiding teams as a CTO.

Had the privilege to enjoy 24.000+ hours of development on solo projects.

SKILLS

O BACK-END DEVELOPMENT SHELL/LINUX (UBUNTU, REDHAT), SHELL/WINDOWS, NODE.JS,

SHELL/WINDOWS, NODE.JS, PHP, APACHE, NGINX, MYSQL, SQLITE, POSTGRESQL, ORACLE

O FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

JAVASCRIPT (ES5, ES6), TYPESCRIPT, PWA, HTML5, CSS3, CANVAS/WEBGL

O ANDROID DEVELOPMENT

JAVA, ANDROID 4.4+

O DESKTOP APPS

WINDOWS POWERSHELL, ELECTRON.JS

o WEB 3

SOLIDITY

O DESIGN/UX/UI

BLENDER, PHOTOSHOP, AUTOMATION SCRIPTS FOR PHOTOSHOP (JAVASCRIPT)

EDUCATION

O B.S. / COMPUTER SCIENCE
"POLITEHNICA" UNIVERSITY,
BUCHAREST, ROMANIA
2008-2012

EXPERIENCE

○ CHIEF TECHNOLOGY OFFICER | NOV. 2021 - PRESENT

METAVERSE GAMES LIMITED

Acqui-hired as the CTO of a Web 3 game development company.

Working on a browser-based MMORPG centered around Web 3 tools.

CHIEF TECHNOLOGY OFFICER | 2014-2021

STEPHINO, INC.

Hired as an early Software Architect, quickly promoted to CTO.

Oversaw the development of a suite of proprietary tools that allowed our team to build and manage 6000+ Android apps on multiple stores.

Our portfolio had more than 100 million total downloads.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER | 2012-2014

STREAMWIDE, S.A.

Youngest Senior Software Developer in the company at age 23.

Created a template engine that was 10x faster than Smarty in official benchmarks. Received the first 100% score in our team at an important performance review.

SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER | 2011 (3 MONTHS)

BRIEFIX

1-man development team at an internet startup. Delivered product using Codelgniter in just 3 months.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER | 2010 (3 MONTHS)

ROLEGAL, S.R.L.

Improved the web presence of one of the largest law offices in Bucharest.